Finding Aid for the Eiko Ishioka papers LSC.2288
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 11: Audiovisual and born-digital material, 1965-2012
  - Subseries 11.3: Audio, 1977-2006, undated
    - Other, 1985-1995, undated (Box 235, Box 236, Box 237, Box 238, Box 239, Box 240, Box 241)
      Labels include: "Dec 8, 1995 Susan Sontag" (microcassette, 235), "Faye Dunaway Interview, Miramar Hotel" (audiocassette, 239), Whitney Houston - Eiko 3/8 0 Tape 1" and "Eiko 3/8/85 Tape 2" (audiocassette, 241), "Napa Valley with Francis Coppola 11/30/85" (audiocassette, 241), "English Lesson" (audiocassette, 238, 240). Some microcassettes (boxes 235-237) appear to be answering machine messages.
    - Unidentified (Box 235, Box 236, Box 237, Box 238, Box 239, Box 240, Box 241)
    - Music CDs (Box 264)
    - Audio equipment (Box 260)
      Includes Sony Walkmans and microcassette recorder.
    - Original housing (or copies of) for microcassettes in boxes 235-236, undated (Box 204, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 11.4: Born-digital, 1985-2011; 285 optical discs (CDs and DVDs with PSD, JPG, TIFF, MOV, VOB, and PDF files, among others); 3 floppy disks; 1 zip disk
    This sub-series contains files related to Ishioka's various design projects. Items include video, photographs, font and color selections, costume sketches, graphic renderings, storyboard renderings, research material, and production notes. Ishioka relied heavily on software such as Adobe Photoshop and QuarkXpress 4.0 to create her graphic renderings and layouts. Many of the files are selections of images of her various works for Eiko on Stage and Eiko by Eiko, as well as design elements for the two books. Ishioka was a frequent conference presenter and this sub-series includes several image selections for Ishioka's presentation slideshows. Personal photographs from trips, parties, and family gatherings are included as well.
    The original file structure was maintained for all items.
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    Appraisal
    Ishioka reused many of the same reference images from project to project, particularly for presentation slideshows and her two books, Eiko on Stage and Eiko by Eiko. Duplicate images were retained in order to preserve their creative context.
    - Cirque du Soleil's Varekai, uclalsc_2288_0141_0001 (Box 141)
      Photographs showcasing various costumes and acts.
    - Cirque du Soleil's Varekai, uclalsc_2288_0141_0003 (Box 141)
      Costume design sketches and photographs of final costumes.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0001 (Box 143)
      Costume design sketches for Green Goblin and various Fury characters.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0002 (Box 143)
      Costume design sketches.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0003 (Box 143)
      Videos of flying workshops for Peter in Arachne's web, Spider-Man and Goblin interacting, and Spider-Man swinging around.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0005 (Box 143)
      Comic book pages featuring drawings and text for the characters titled Carnage, Electro, and Lizard that appear to have been used for research.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0006 (Box 143)
      Reference photographs and drawings of lizards for the Lizard character's costume design.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0008 (Box 143)
      Costume design sketches and reference photographs for Spider-Man, Green Goblin, and other characters.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0009 (Box 143)
      Images of preliminary scenic concepts and a PDF of preliminary scenic concept script that provides text on each scene's location, character movement and blocking, as well as some set design sketches.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0010 (Box 143)
      Character and costume design sketches for villains.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0011 (Box 143)
      Video clips of acrobatic flying acts during rehearsal workshop, in which Julie Taymor and Ishioka make an appearance. Clips include footage of Spider-Man and Aranche interacting, Aranche in web, Spider-Man bouncing off the walls, making of the loom, loom twirling. Also includes footage of leadership talking about set design and flying direction.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0143_0013 (Box 143)
      Costume design sketches and 3-D models for villains and other characters.
    - Winter Olympics, Salt Lake City, uclalsc_2288_0148_0001 (Box 148)
      Graphic renderings of uniforms for Spanish, Japanese, and Canadian teams.
    - Houston Rockets, 2002 Winter Olympics (Salt Lake City), uclalsc_2288_0148_0002 (Box 148)
      Images related to the Houston Rockets, logo design, 3D models of the team's uniform designs, the team playing basketball, and Houston Rockets Power Dancers posing in their uniforms with the logo design. Also includes 3D models of uniform designs for Beijing Olympic opening ceremonies.
    - Houston Rockets, uclalsc_2288_0148_0003 (Box 148)
      Images of 3D models of Houston Rocket uniform designs.
    - Houston Rockets, uclalsc_2288_0148_0004 (Box 148)
      Photographs of the Houston Rockets playing basketball against the Los Angeles Lakers at the Toyota Center. There are also photographs of the Houston Rockets logo design on the basketball court and on the uniforms of the Houston Rockets basketball players and dancers.
    - Houston Rockets, uclalsc_2288_0148_0005 (Box 148)
      Houston Rocket poster designs, poster background designs, and cover designs, some of which feature images of basketball players.
    - Houston Rockets, uclalsc_2288_0148_0006 (Box 148)
      Images of all sides of the "Away" (red) and "Home" (white) Houston Rockets basketball uniform designs, and images and PostScript text file of the Houston Rockets logo.
    - Nike advertising, uclalsc_2288_0152_0001 (Box 152)
      Photographs of football players wearing warrior masks.
    - Nike advertising, uclalsc_2288_0152_0002 (Box 152)
      Sketch designs of Nike warrior masks.
    - Headshots of Ishioka by Brigitte Lacombe, uclalsc_2288_0198_0001 (Box 198)
    - Toyota lecture, uclalsc_2288_0257_0001 (Box 257)
      Second part of the Toyota Series Lecture by Ishioka discussing her career's work and her book Eiko on Stage at ArtCenter, followed by brief Q&A.
    - Toyota lecture, uclalsc_2288_0257_0002 (Box 257)
      First part of the Toyota Series Lecture by Ishioka discussing her career's work and her book Eiko on Stage at ArtCenter, followed by brief Q&A.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0259_0001 (Box 259)
      Selection of images for the book. including Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, various sets, and of the red bodysuit costume from The Cell.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0259_0002 (Box 259)
      Images related to Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0259_0003 (Box 259)
      Images related to M. Butterfly and Bram Stoker's Dracula.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0259_0004 (Box 259)
      Images from the set of Dreams & Nightmares and of Dracula's golden robe in Bram Stoker's Dracula.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0259_0005 (Box 259)
      Images from the set of Dreams & Nightmares; costumes from Chushingura and The Ring of the Nibelung.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0259_0006 (Box 259)
      Images from Eiko on Stage of costumes and costume design sketch from The Cell and Richard Wagner's 'Der Ring des Nibelungen.
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0259_0007 (Box 259)
      Video footage of the musical production.
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life, uclalsc_2288_0259_0008 (Box 259)
      Video of NHK documentary about the musical, with interviews from various people including Ishioka.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0009 (Box 259)
      Selections of images for the book, including poster designed for Parco Issey Miyake campaign and book designs.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0010 (Box 259)
      Selections of various graphic and poster designs for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0011 (Box 259)
      Images related to book and periodical designs selected for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0012 (Box 259)
      Selections of design work on Parco, magazine covers, posters, and more for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0013 (Box 259)
      Selection of images of package design projects for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0014 (Box 259)
      Photograph of book design.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0015 (Box 259)
      Selection of images related to exhibition work for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0016 (Box 259)
      Selection of images of design work for Parco, magazine layouts, and posters for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0017 (Box 259)
      Selection of images of magazine designs for the book, as well as costume design sketches for Cirque du Soleil's Varekai.
    - Parco campaigns and Leni Riefenstahl exhibit, uclalsc_2288_0259_0018 (Box 259)
      Images of campaigns designed for Parco and one image of the exhibit curated for Leni Riefenstahl.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0019 (Box 259)
      Images of design work for Parco that were selected for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0020 (Box 259)
      Images of poster designs that were selected for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0021 (Box 259)
      Images of book and magazine design work selected for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0022 (Box 259)
      Images of book and magazine designs selected for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0259_0023 (Box 259)
      Images of artwork and package design work selected for the book.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0259_0024 (Box 259)
      Photographs of characters from the film in costume, including the Masked Bandit, Alexandria, and the soldiers.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0259_0025 (Box 259)
      Photographs of characters from the film in costume, including the Masked Bandit, Alexandria, and Luigi.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0259_0026 (Box 259)
      Photographs of characters from the film in costume, including Luigi and Roy Walker.
    - Leni Riefenstahl, uclalsc_2288_0259_0027 (Box 259)
      Image of the Leni Riefenstahl exhibit.
    - Images of Ishioka's poster designs, uclalsc_2288_0259_0028 (Box 259)
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0259_0029 (Box 259)
      Photographs of characters from the film in costume, including the Masked Bandit and Alexandria.
    - Leni Riefenstahl exhibition and Tutu record design, uclalsc_2288_0259_0030 (Box 259)
      Images of Tutu record and photographs from the Leni Riefenstahl exhibit.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0259_0031 (Box 259)
      Photographs of actors in costume.
    - Images of poster and book design work, uclalsc_2288_0259_0032 (Box 259)
    - Package, book, and record cover design, uclalsc_2288_0259_0033 (Box 259)
      Images include design work for Tutu record cover.
    - Parco and Tutu, uclalsc_2288_0259_0034 (Box 259)
      Images from Parco advertisements and Miles Davis' Tutu record design.
    - Eiko International Design Conference presentation, uclalsc_2288_0259_0035 (Box 259)
      Photographs of Ishioka giving presentations and at a receptions. Also includes documents with her curriculum vitae and lecture notes.
    - Shiju Hosho: event/party photographs, uclalsc_2288_0259_0036 (Box 259)
    - Slideshow working files, uclalsc_2288_0259_0037 (Box 259)
      Photographs and thumbnails of Ishioka's various graphic design and film projects created during the 1970s.
    - Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark, uclalsc_2288_0259_0038 (Box 259)
      Costume design sketches of the front and back of Spider-Man's costume.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0001 (Box 261)
      Press videos for The Fall, including video clips of Tarsem Singh and Ishioka discussing the film.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0261_0002 (Box 261)
      Second part of an episode of The Proposal for the Future about the Beijing Olympics, including footage of the opening ceremonies, behind-the-scenes footage leading up to the opening ceremonies, and an interview with Zhang Yimou.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0261_0003 (Box 261)
      First part of an episode of The Proposal for the Future about the Beijing Olympics, including footage of the opening ceremonies, behind-the-scenes footage leading up to the opening ceremonies, and an interview with Zhang Yimou.
    - Cirque du Soleil's Varekai research material, uclalsc_2288_0261_0005 (Box 261)
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0261_0007 (Box 261)
      NBC coverage of the opening ceremonies.
    - Immortals, uclalsc_2288_0261_0009 (Box 261)
      Photographs taken on the film set of Immortals, including images during filming, a crew photograph, and images of Ishioka on set.
    - Immortals, uclalsc_2288_0261_0010 (Box 261)
      Photographs taken on the film set of Immortals, including images of filming, cast being dressed, people painting masks and preparing costumes. Also includes images of some costume sketches.
    - Immortals, uclalsc_2288_0261_0011 (Box 261)
      Costume design sketches for Immortals.
    - Immortals, uclalsc_2288_0261_0012 (Box 261)
      Images of Zeus character in costume pieces.
    - Mirror Mirror, uclalsc_2288_0261_0013 (Box 261)
      Images of costumes, film stills, and behind the scenes photographs on the set of the film.
    - Ishioka's emails, uclalsc_2288_0261_0014 (Box 261)
      Includes 4,000 emails primarily related to Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark and Cirque du Soleil collaboration with Criss Angel at the Luxor Hotel.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0261_0015 (Box 261)
      Selection of images of design work for Parco, magazine covers for the book.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0016 (Box 261)
      Photographs of characters from the film in costume.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0017 (Box 261)
      Photographs of the character Otta Benga in costume.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0018 (Box 261)
      Photographs of characters from the film in costume, including Otta Benga and Darwin.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0019 (Box 261)
      Photographs of Sister Evelyn in costume.
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0020 (Box 261)
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0021 (Box 261)
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0022 (Box 261)
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0023 (Box 261)
    - The Fall, uclalsc_2288_0261_0024 (Box 261)
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0261_0025 (Box 261)
      Part 1 of 4 video of NHK coverage of the 2008 Beijing Olympics opening ceremony.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0261_0026 (Box 261)
      Part 2 of 4 video of NHK coverage of the 2008 Beijing Olympics opening ceremony.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0261_0027 (Box 261)
      Part 3 of 4 video of NHK coverage of the 2008 Beijing Olympics opening ceremony.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0261_0028 (Box 261)
      Part 4 of 4 video of NHK coverage of the 2008 Beijing Olympics opening ceremony.
    - 62nd Tony Awards, uclalsc_2288_0261_0029 (Box 261)
      Video of the 2008 Tony Awards with Japanese subtitles and voiceover commentary.
    - Tamara de Lempicka: The Myth of the Portrait, uclalsc_2288_0261_0030 (Box 261)
      Video footage of Japanese talk show, including segments in which Ishioka is interviewed and discusses her work on the book.
    - 62nd Tony Awards, uclalsc_2288_0261_0033 (Box 261)
      Video clips of the second half of 2010 Tony Awards show, with added segments by two hosts interviewing different nominees, including Ishioka.
    - 62nd Tony Awards, uclalsc_2288_0261_0035 (Box 261)
      Video clips of the first half of 2010 Tony Awards show, with added segments by two hosts interviewing different nominees, including Ishioka.
    - Chushingura, uclalsc_2288_0261_0043 (Box 261)
      Photographs of the play, including images of sets alone.
    - Chushingura, uclalsc_2288_0261_0044 (Box 261)
    - Houston Rockets, uclalsc_2288_0261_0045 (Box 261)
      Photographs of Houston Rockets playing basketball in their red and white uniforms designed by Ishioka; 3D computer graphic models of the Houston Rockets uniforms and an image of the Houston Rockets logo.
    - The Ring of the Nibelung and Chushingura, uclalsc_2288_0261_0046 (Box 261)
      Includes images of costume pieces.
    - The Ring of the Nibelung, uclalsc_2288_0261_0047 (Box 261)
    - Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, uclalsc_2288_0261_0048 (Box 261)
      Behind the scenes photographs of the filming of Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters.
    - The Cell, uclalsc_2288_0261_0050 (Box 261)
      Costume design sketches and photographs.
    - M. Butterfly, uclalsc_2288_0261_0051 (Box 261)
      Images from M. Butterfly, including costumes, characters on set, and a butterfly design.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0261_0052 (Box 261)
      Images of magazine design work selected for the book.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0261_0053 (Box 261)
    - Leni Riefenstahl exhibition and Tutu record design, uclalsc_2288_0261_0056 (Box 261)
      Photographs of design work for Tutu; images of posters for Erco We Make Light Work, Close Up of Japan, L'Inhumaine and Koyaanisqatsi; two images of posters announcing book and exhibition, Tamara de Lempicka: The Myth of the Portrait; and an image of the font used for poster for Bram Stoker's Dracula.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0261_0057 (Box 261)
      Images selected for the first chapter of the book, "Apocalypse to Innocence".
    - Criss Angel and Cirque du Soleil Luxor Hotel show, uclalsc_2288_0261_0059 (Box 261)
      Images of reference artwork and photographs for Luxor show.
    - Criss Angel Mindfreak, uclalsc_2288_0261_0060 (Box 261)
      Criss Angel photography compilation for Cirque du Soleil, including photos of "The Dream," "Mindfreak TV," "Worlds," "Potential Characters," "Other Illusions," character costume designs, and reference artwork.
    - Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters: A Life in Four Chapters, uclalsc_2288_0261_0061 (Box 261)
      Black and white photographs on the set of Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0261_0062 (Box 261)
      Selection of images from David Copperfield's Dreams & Nightmares for the book.
    - Bram Stoker's Dracula, uclalsc_2288_0261_0063 (Box 261)
      Includes costume design sketches and film stills of actors in costume.
    - Bram Stoker's Dracula, uclalsc_2288_0261_0065 (Box 261)
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0261_0066 (Box 261)
      Selection of images for the book of design work for Parco, Alfa, package design, and Tokyo poster design.
    - Bram Stoker's Dracula, uclalsc_2288_0261_0067 (Box 261)
    - Photographs from Ishoka's life and work, uclalsc_2288_0261_0068 (Box 261)
      Personal photographs as well as images related to her work for the Houston Rockets, Apocalypse Now, Bram Stoker's Dracula Cirque de Soleil's Varekai, Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, the Winter Olympics, Salt Lake City, Leni Riefenstahl's exhibition, and Miles Davis' Tutu.
    - Teresa, el cuerpo de Cristo, uclalsc_2288_0261_0069 (Box 261)
      Press clippings about the film Theresa: The Body of Christ.
    - Eiko by Eiko, uclalsc_2288_0261_0070 (Box 261)
      Images of book cover and a selection of its contents.
    - Björk's "Cocoon" music video, uclalsc_2288_0261_0071 (Box 261)
      Film stills from the music video.
    - Hurricane tour, uclalsc_2288_0261_0072 (Box 261)
      Photographs from Grace Jones's tour wearing the costumes designed by Ishioka, who appears in some of the photographs.
    - Chushingura, uclalsc_2288_0261_0075 (Box 261)
      Images of sets, costumes, and playbill related to the play.
    - Documentary about Ishioka's work, uclalsc_2288_0262_0001 (Box 262)
      Content focused mostly on her work for Spider-Man: Turn Off the Dark.
    - Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters, The Ring of the Nibelung Leni Riefenstahl book cover, and Tokyo Form & Spirit, uclalsc_2288_0262_0012 (Box 262)
      Images related to these projects.
    - Images related to various projects, uclalsc_2288_0262_0013 (Box 262)
      Projects include Ishioka's work for Apocalypse Now poster, exhibits, and stage designs.
    - Images related to various projects, uclalsc_2288_0262_0014 (Box 262)
    - Winter Olympics, Salt Lake City, uclalsc_2288_0262_0015 (Box 262)
      Photographs related to design work on uniforms for the Salt Lake City Olympics, including images of costume designs and athletes in their uniforms.
    - Winter Olympics, Salt Lake City, uclalsc_2288_0262_0016 (Box 262)
      Image of Time magazine cover with Catriona Le May Doan and Jeremy Wotherspoon of the Canadian teams wearing their uniforms designed by Ishioka.
    - Tutu record cover design and Dreams & Nightmares, uclalsc_2288_0262_0017 (Box 262)
      Images related to the Miles Davis' album cover artwork and David Copperfield's act.
    - Björk's "Cocoon" music video, uclalsc_2288_0262_0018 (Box 262)
      Costume design sketches for the music video.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0262_0019 (Box 262)
      Slideshow video with music and images of uniforms designed for the opening ceremonies.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0262_0020 (Box 262)
      Digital video recordings of footage of the opening ceremonies, NBC news show, and Food Network cooking show with commercials.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0262_0021 (Box 262)
      Video footage of opening ceremonies.
    - Summer Olympics, Beijing, uclalsc_2288_0262_0023 (Box 262)
      Video of NBC coverage of the opening ceremonies.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0024 (Box 262)
      Selection of images for the book of costume from The Cell, sets from M. Butterfly and Dreams & Nightmares.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0025 (Box 262)
      Information and images of fonts and color themes selected for the book.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0026 (Box 262)
      Selection of images for the book, including film stills from Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters and book jacket and logo designs.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0027 (Box 262)
      Selection of images for the book, including computer-rendered graphics used as design storyboard for Chushingura and film stills from Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0028 (Box 262)
      Selection of images for the book related to Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0029 (Box 262)
      Selection of images for the book, including film stills from Bram Stoker's Dracula and sets from M. Butterfly.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0030 (Box 262)
      Selection of images for the book, including costume design sketches and photographs from Bram Stoker's Dracula, and set design for Dreams & Nightmares.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0031 (Box 262)
      Selection of images for the book related to sets and costume pieces from Dreams & Nightmares, Chushingura and The Ring of the Nibelung.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0032 (Box 262)
      Selection of images for the book, including photographs from the set of Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters; photographs and costume design sketch of costumes from The Cell and Varekai.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0033 (Box 262)
      Selection of film stills from Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters for the book.
    - Eiko on Stage, uclalsc_2288_0262_0034 (Box 262)